# Resume for Jessica Haapoja

### Lives in Minnesota

Email: jl.haapoja@gmail.com

#### **Experience and Skills**

Adobe products: Photoshop, Illustrator, Animate, premier pro and InDesign. HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Final cut, and Blender. The Dewey Decimal System. Experience with several craft/hobbies: polymer clay and refinishing/restoring furniture. Skilled at organization and money management.

-See portfolio website to view some of my work-

#### Education

Currently a student at St. Paul Community College - expected to graduate summer 2023.

Attended Metropolitan State University through the PSEO program senior year of high school.

Graduated from Minnesota Connections Academy on 6-2-2021.

#### **Work Experience**

### Working retail - June 2021 to present

Expanded customer service skills by assisting customers in locating materials, and answering questions regarding, specific merchandise, weekly sale's and return policy.

Learned how to display Merchandise in appealing, and space effective ways through consolidating and setting seasonal areas.

## Library Assistant Volunteer; 06/20/2017 - 08/09/2017 Anoka County Library, Coon Rapids, Mn

Gained knowledge of teamwork and education through group projects.

Acquired promotion skills by creatively setting up displays for library summer events.

#### **Extra-Curricular**

Took French for three years in high school and In middle school took part in Thespian Society for two years. Participated in girl scouts for eight years and Did Violin for three years.

## **Honors**

On St. Paul college dean's list from fall 2021-fall 2022 and on the high school Honor Roll from 2017 to 2021. Received the Girl Scout Silver Award.

# **Community Volunteer**

Volunteered at the Anoka County Library Crooked Lake Branch from June - august of 2017. Also volunteered with Unity North Spiritual Center and Girl Scouts MN River Valley.

--References available upon request--